<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="side_plank">
        Benifits of Plank \n1) Helps improve your posture.\n2) Might provide flexibility.\n3) Helps reduce belly fat.\n4) It can help strenthen your core.\n5) Can help reduce joint and especially back pain.\n6) It can help improve metabolism.

    </string>
    <string name="lunges">
        Benifits of Lunges \n1) Helps strengthen your lower body.\n2) Increase core strength.\n3) Helps improve posture.\n4) Alignment and Symmetry.\n5) Weight Loss.\n6) Balance and Stability

    </string>
    <string name="stepping">
        Benifits of Stepping \n1) Helps improve cardiovascular health.\n2) Might provide a full-body workout.\n3) Aids in weight management and fat loss.\n4) Can enhance lower body strength, including legs and glutes.\n5) Improves overall stamina and endurance.\n6) Enhances balance and coordination.

    </string>

    <string name="abs_crunches">
        Benifits of abs crunches \n1) Strengthens abdominal muscles, including rectus abdominis.\n2) May improve posture and core stability.\n3) Helps reduce belly fat when combined with a balanced diet.\n4) Enhances overall core strength and endurance. \n5) Can relieve lower back pain by strengthening core muscles.\n6) Promotes better balance and stability.

    </string>

    <string name="push_ups">
        Benifits of push ups  \n1) Strengthens abdominal muscles, including rectus abdominis.\n2) May improve posture and core stability.\n3) Helps reduce belly fat when combined with a balanced diet.\n4) Enhances overall core strength and endurance.\n5) Can relieve lower back pain by strengthening core muscles.\n6) Promotes better balance and stability.
    </string>

    <string name="mediterian_plan">
    The Mediterranean diet has long been considered the gold standard for nutrition, disease prevention, wellness, and longevity. This is based on its nutrition benefits and sustainability.
    \n\n
    <b>How it works</b>
    \n
    The Mediterranean diet is based on foods that people in countries like Italy and Greece have traditionally eaten. It is rich in:
    \n- vegetables
    \n- fruits
    \n- whole grains
    \n- fish
    \n- nuts
    \n- lentils
    \n- olive oil
    \n\n
    Foods such as poultry, eggs, and dairy products are to be eaten in moderation, and red meats are limited.
    \n\n
    Additionally, the Mediterranean diet limits:
    \n\n
    - refined grains
    - trans fats
    - processed meats
    - added sugar
    - other highly processed foods
    \n\n
    <b>Health benefits</b>
    \n
    This diet’s emphasis on minimally processed foods and plants has been associated with a reduced risk of multiple chronic diseases and increased life expectancy. Studies also show that the Mediterranean diet has a preventive effect against certain cancers (1Trusted Source).
    \n\n
    Though the diet was designed to lower heart disease risk, numerous studies indicate that its plant-based, high unsaturated fat dietary pattern can also aid in weight loss (2).
</string>


    <string name="dash_plan">
    Dietary Approaches to Stop Hypertension, or DASH, is an eating plan designed to help treat or prevent high blood pressure, which is clinically known as hypertension.
    \n\n
    It emphasizes eating plenty of fruits, vegetables, whole grains, and lean meats. It is low in salt, red meat, added sugars, and fat.
    \n\n
    While the DASH diet is not a weight loss diet, many people report losing weight on it.
    \n\n
    <b>How it works</b>
    \n
    The DASH diet recommends specific servings of different food groups. The number of servings you are encouraged to eat depends on your daily calorie intake.
    \n\n
    For example, each day an average person on the DASH diet would eat about:
    \n- five servings of vegetables
    \n- five servings of fruit
    \n- seven servings of healthy carbs like whole grains
    \n- two servings of low fat dairy products
    \n- two servings or fewer of lean meats
    \n\n
    In addition, it’s recommended to consume nuts and seeds two to three times per week (7Trusted Source).
    \n\n
    <b>Health benefits</b>
    \n
    The DASH diet has been shown to reduce blood pressure levels and several heart disease risk factors. Also, it may help lower your risk of breast and colorectal cancers (7Trusted Source, 8Trusted Source, 9Trusted Source, 10Trusted Source, 11Trusted Source).
    \n\n
    Studies show that the DASH diet can also help you lose weight.

    </string>

    <string name="plant_plan">
    Vegetarianism and veganism are the most popular versions of plant-based diets, which restrict animal products for health, ethical, and environmental reasons.
    \n\n
    However, more flexible plant-based diets also exist, such as the flexitarian diet. This is a plant-based diet that allows eating animal products in moderation.
    \n\n
    <b>How it works</b>
    \n
    Typical vegetarian diets restrict meat of all kinds but allow dairy products. Typical vegan diets restrict all animal products, including dairy, butter, and sometimes other byproducts like honey.
    \n\n
    The flexitarian eating plan does not have clear-cut rules or recommendations about calories and macronutrients, so it’s considered more of a lifestyle than a diet. Its principles include:
    \n- consuming protein from plants instead of animals
    \n- eating mostly fruits, vegetables, legumes, and whole grains
    \n- eating the least processed, most natural forms of foods
    \n- limiting sugar and sweets
    \n
    Additionally, it allows the flexibility to consume meat and animal products from time to time.
    \n\n
    <b>Health benefits</b>
    \n
    Numerous studies have shown that plant-based diets can reduce your risk of developing chronic diseases, including improved markers of metabolic health, decreased blood pressure, and reduced risk of type 2 diabetes. They can also help you lose weight.

    </string>

    <string name="mind_plan">
    Vegetarianism and veganism are the most popular versions of plant-based diets, which restrict animal products for health, ethical, and environmental reasons.
    \n\n
    However, more flexible plant-based diets also exist, such as the flexitarian diet. This is a plant-based diet that allows eating animal products in moderation.
    \n\n
    <b>How it works</b>
    \n
    Typical vegetarian diets restrict meat of all kinds but allow dairy products. Typical vegan diets restrict all animal products, including dairy, butter, and sometimes other byproducts like honey.
    \n\n
    The flexitarian eating plan does not have clear-cut rules or recommendations about calories and macronutrients, so it’s considered more of a lifestyle than a diet. Its principles include:
    \n- consuming protein from plants instead of animals
    \n- eating mostly fruits, vegetables, legumes, and whole grains
    \n- eating the least processed, most natural forms of foods
    \n- limiting sugar and sweets
    \n
    Additionally, it allows the flexibility to consume meat and animal products from time to time.
    \n\n
    <b>Health benefits</b>
    \n
    Numerous studies have shown that plant-based diets can reduce your risk of developing chronic diseases, including improved markers of metabolic health, decreased blood pressure, and reduced risk of type 2 diabetes. They can also help you lose weight.


    </string>

    <string name="inter_plan">
    The Mediterranean-DASH Intervention for Neurodegenerative Delay (MIND) diet combines aspects of the Mediterranean and DASH diets to create an eating pattern that focuses on brain health.
    \n\n
    <b>How it works</b>
    \n
    Like the flexitarian diet, the MIND diet does not have a strict meal plan, but instead encourages eating 10 specific foods with brain health benefits.
    \n
    Per week, MIND includes eating:
    \n- six or more servings of green, leafy vegetables
    \n- one serving of non-starchy vegetables
    \n- five or more servings of nuts
    \n
    Other foods it encourages multiple times a week include:
    \n- berries
    \n- beans
    \n- olive oil
    \n- whole grains
    \n- fish
    \n- poultry
    \n\n
    <b>Health benefits</b>
    \n
    Research shows that the MIND diet may reduce a person’s risk of developing Alzheimer’s disease, and studies show that the MIND diet is superior to other plant-rich diets for improving cognition (20Trusted Source, 21Trusted Source).
    \n\n
    Research also shows that the MIND diet can help slow cognitive decline and improve resiliency in older adults.


    </string>

    <string name="vol_plan">
    The Volumetrics diet was created by Penn State University nutrition professor Barbara Rolls and is meant to be a long-term lifestyle change rather than a strict diet.
    \n\n
    <b>How it works</b>
    \n
    The eating plan is designed to promote weight loss by having you fill up on nutrient-dense foods that are low in calories and high in water. Meanwhile, it limits calorie-dense foods like cookies, candies, nuts, seeds, and oils.
    \n
    The Volumetrics diet divides food into four categories based on food’s calorie density, which can be calculated with a formula created by Rolls. These categories are:
    \n
    <b>Category one:</b> includes foods of very low calorie density, like non-starchy fruits and vegetables, nonfat milk, and broth-based soup
    \n
    <b>Category two:</b> includes low calorie-dense foods, like starchy fruits and vegetables, grains, breakfast cereal, low fat meat, legumes, and low fat mixed dishes like chili
    \n
    <b>Category three:</b> includes medium calorie-dense foods, like meat, cheese, pizza, bread, and ice cream
    \n
    <b>Category four:</b> includes high calorie-dense foods, like crackers, chips, chocolate candies, nuts, butter, and oil
    \n
    Meals on the Volumetric diet consist mostly of foods from categories one and two, with limited amounts of food from categories three and four. No foods are completely off-limits on the Volumetrics diet, and exercise is encouraged for at least 30–60 minutes each day.
    \n

</string>



</resources>